yeepgame.com 2016-01-08

# Privacy Policy-Yeepgame.com-Play free online game; build your own kingdom in Yeepgame!

Yeepgame absolutely respects and ensures the privacy of your information on the internet and your own personal privacy. To better help you understand how we collect, use, and protect the information you give to us, please read the following Privacy Policy.

**1.       ** **What information we gather**

 We gather personal information from all registering members. We will request your email address when registering for your account safety concern. Besides, gender, birthday, country and phone number are all optional for you to fill in our “[Ucenter](http://www.yeepgame.com/ucenter/index)”.

We also collect data relating to all network connections, primarily your IP address. We use this information to track fraudulent user activity (including but not limited to: the use of multiple accounts, account sharing, illegal forum activity.) Your browser type and version are also detected to better enhance your user experience.

Please keep in mind that if you disclose personal information through our messaging system or public forms - this information could be collected and used by other parties.

**2.  How we use your personal information**

Yeepgame never sells or shares any of your personal information with other parties. We take all necessary measures to protect your personal information by deploying safe network models for storing and retrieving data. All information is strictly for internal use and all e-mails are only sent from our facilities.

Yeepgame won’t access and/or disclose your personal information without your permission except that it is required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on our company or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of our company, including the Yeepgame website; or (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of Yeepgame, its web sites, or the public.

**3.** **Use Google Cookies**  
A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a Web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.

Yeepgame uses cookies to save certain information and tract data. Yeepgame uses cookies to track visitor numbers and your current web browser, usage of the website and your website preference. We never use cookies to gather or share your personal information.

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, certain features of Yeepgame may not be accessible for you –as our site requires them to function properly and prevent site abuse. 

**4.  Protecting Yourself   
**If you follow links or ads on our site that link to other websites, please be sure that you are familiar with their own privacy policies; our privacy policy does not apply to any external sites.

Please keep your account and password private and do not give such information to anyone else easily. If you're using a shared computer, remember to log out and close out of all game windows to protect your personal information.

As the forums are visible to the public please be aware that any personal information written in the public plate can be seen by the third parties.

**5.   Modification of Privacy Policy  
**Yeepgame reserves the right to change or delete portions of this Privacy Policy at any time, as well as make any additions to it. We will attempt to notify you of any such update or modification. However, you are responsible for periodically reviewing our Privacy Policy. You use of the site and/or any products or services offered by Yeepgame signifies your assent to the updated or modified Privacy Policy.

**6\. OPT OUT/CORRECTIONS**

Upon your request, we can (a) correct or update your personal information; (b) stop sending emails to your email address; and/or (c) disable your account to prevent any future purchases through that account. You can make these requests by emailing to Yeegame’s Customer Support - [gs@yeepgame.com](mailto:service@seasonmall.com)   .
